arrl.org 2013-06-21

# Privacy Policy

**  
We Respect Your Privacy**

At ARRL, we are committed to providing you with superior products and services, along with the peace of mind knowing that the security of your personal information is our top priority. We understand your concerns about guarding information about you and we want to assure you that we have taken steps and will continue to take steps, to safeguard that information.

**1\. What Personal Information Do We Collect?**

In connection with applications for Amateur Radio licenses those granted by the Federal Communications Commission or ARRL products and services, it is necessary that we collect certain personal information about you. We obtain this information from applications and other forms you submit to us and from other sources, such as our Web site. We obtain information such as your name, address, date of birth, e-mail address, social security number or employer identification number and credit or debit card number, as necessary to perform services on your behalf, to make our products and services more conveniently available to you, or to fulfill Federal Communications Commission requirements. “Personal information” does not include information that is lawfully obtained from publicly available sources, or from federal, state or local government records lawfully made available to the general public.

  **2\. Is Personal Information Shared with Others?**

For amateur radio license applications, we are required to share the collected information with the Federal Communications Commission. ARRL respects your privacy and we will not share personal information we collect about you except as required by law or with your permission. ARRL shares public data but not personal information with our corporate partners. We provide these companies with only those elements of public information they need to offer or deliver services. We do not permit disclosure of private data to others. 

  **3\. How Do We Protect the Confidentiality, Security and Integrity of Personal Information?**

ARRL safeguards personal information contained in both paper and electronic records. Properly securing the information we collect is a primary commitment. We meet security and privacy standards for both e-commerce and personal information, ensuring the security and confidentiality of such information in a manner consistent with industry practices.

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the information we collect. Access to such information is restricted to authorized employees and agents of ARRL who need it in order to perform transactions related to Amateur Radio licenses or to provide products or services to you. These employees and agents are trained in the proper handling of such information.

**4\. Changes to this Privacy Statement**

ARRL may at any time, without notice and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of ARRL’s website after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

**5.** **Questions or Suggestions** ****  
  
If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at [privacy@arrl.org](mailto:privacy@arrl.org).

Last updated: January 1, 2009

 **_______________________________________________________________**

## ARRL Online Privacy Policy
